Fishermen and sailors sometimes claim to have seen monsters in the sea.
Though people have often laughed at stories told by seamen, it is now known that many of these 'monsters' which have at times been sighted are simply strange fish.
Occasionally, unusual creatures are washed to the shore, but they are rarely caught out at sea.
Some time ago, however, a peculiar fish was caught near Madagascar.
A small f ishing boat was carried miles out to sea by the powerful fish as it pulled on the line.
Realizing that this was no ordinary fish, the fisherman made every effort not to damage it in any way.
When it was eventually brought to shore, it was found to be over thirteen feet long.
It had a head like a horse, big blue eyes, shining silver skin, and a bright red tail.
The fish, which has since been sent to a museum where it is being examined by a scientist, is called an oarfish.
Such creatures have rarely been seen alive by man as they live at a depth of six hundred feet.